All right, here's how I run meta ads to
get clients for my $199,000 a month go
high level agency. So, I'm going to go
through uh how to create winning ads, ad
account set uh setup and structure, how
to scale [clears throat] your ads, and
then a couple core lessons. Um, let me
refresh this page real quick just so you
guys can see this is legit. Uh, so 199K
here, 187 uh revenue last month. And
then for everyone that says I make all
my money off affiliates, let me go here.
Uh, I don't know why it's $0, but last
month I made about $9,000 off affiliate.
It's also not even the same payment
processor. Anyway, I'm going to go to
Stripe as well and refresh this. We're
also in the middle of switching payment
processors. So, Stripe is going to be
messed up. Uh, you can see net volume
last month was about 190K. And then this
month we're going for about 199. And by
the way, if you guys are listening to
anyone on YouTube who's not refreshing
their payment processor and showing you
like the stats, don't listen to them.
Like if they're not refreshing their
[__] and showing you their processor of
what they're making, like I'll have
months on here where I refresh my
processor and I'll be making less than I
was the month before or the video
before, it doesn't matter. It's about
just being transparent and showing
exactly what's working and what we're
doing. But anyway, so here's uh here's
what we're covering. So, how to create
winning ads, ad account setup and
structure, how to scale your ads, and
then some core lessons. So, first off,
how to create winning ads. Okay, so I
use a tool uh called app.ads library. Uh
there's a free version of it. I pay for
it. It's like a hundred bucks a year,
but this tool is like it's just it's the
best freaking tool in the world. It's so
worth it. So, I'll click Facebook, I'll
click Instagram. Um, we want to look for
ads. Uh, and by the way, anytime I know
we need winning ads, this is like the
first place I come to to get ideas from
people. That being said, like this does
not give you an excuse to freaking copy
people word for word. Like, don't copy
their VSSL and their hook and their and
their entire messaging and their offer
and their landing page. Like, use them
as inspiration. So, I'll come here. I'll
type contractors because we work with
home service businesses. We want to make
sure we find an ad that's running for at
least 30 days. Actually, usually I'll do
60 plus days actually. So, I'll do 60
plus. Uh we want uh we want still
running. And then we want uh spend
doesn't matter. Format. We want I I'll
usually do video if I'm doing video ads.
So, I'll come here. I'll see video ads
here. I'll literally just click this ad.
If your concrete company is already
doing a million a year or more, but you
still find yourself hustling to keep the
pipeline full, this message is for you.
Most
>> that's his hook right there, right? And
we know this has been been running for
132 days. So, I'm going to basically
either I'll just copy that hook directly
and then put my own body on it or I'll
just like literally like take his
messaging and if his messaging works for
our industry, I'll tweak it slightly,
but I'll I'll use the same general
creative so I know it's me looking
directly at the camera, saying that hook
and then whatever messaging I want,
right? Or whatever whatever whatever uh
messaging that I come up with. But the
point is is I'm getting my initial idea
from this creative. Okay, so let's
scroll down here as well. Let's see this
one. Uh uh uh how about this one? I'll
click this one. So, this one's been
running for 195 days, so we know this ad
works.
>> What do you do when you get hundreds of
leads month after month, but little to
no sales? That's what almost every
residential contractor is experiencing
when they start to spend over $1,000 a
day in ads.
>> Okay, so this this this hook doesn't
really apply to us, so I'm just going to
skip this, right? But this is like this
is genuinely the exact process I go
through. I will just keep scrolling down
here and keep finding people that
already market for contractors. And like
here's an example right here. So, I
haven't really used much like uh many
banners in my ads. So, I know this ad
obviously works cuz it's been running
for a long time. So, I'm going to try a
banner. Obviously, I'll switch the
messaging, but this is a unique idea
that we haven't really tried yet. So,
now I'm going to put a banner in my ad.
I'm going to copy this guy's hook, and
then I'm going to put my own variation
and my own spin on it. That being said,
I might still copy, see how he's close
to the camera. He's obviously filming
with his phone like this with like some
kind of a decent background behind him.
I'll just copy that, right? And just use
my own version. and I'll just repeat
this process until I have a bunch of ads
that I think will win and then I'll go
test them. Um, okay. So, ad account
structure. Uh, so let me go over here
and actually show you the ad account.
So, what we've been doing is there's
actually two different ways. There's CBO
and there's [__] So, notoriously, you
can see here we've been doing uh [__]
which is one ad, one ad set, and we will
literally just run one ad per adset,
start at $30 a day, and then scale it as
high as we can. Um, that being said,
with the Andromeda update, we've
switched over to CBO campaigns. So the
difference is the CBO campaign basically
the budget is held at the campaign level
as opposed to one ad per adset, right?
So with the adset budget, you can
literally have more control because you
can say, "Hey, I know this ad is going
to get this much spend." With the CBO
campaign, because the because the spend
is at the campaign level, basically what
you're doing is you're just throwing all
of your winning ads into one campaign,
closing your [__] eyes, and just
praying it works. That being said, like
Facebook's AI is so good at getting you
results that honestly it's been working
really well for us. And that's kind of
what we're trying to transition over to.
Um so yeah, basically all the winning
ads we've ever had, we'll throw them in
one CBO campaign and just let it rip. Um
anywhere from $100 to $300 a day. Uh
that's pretty much how we structure our
ad account. And that's how we scale our
ads. And when we're scaling our ads to
find a winner, you always want to find
flow before you find friction. Uh okay,
so what does that mean? So flow means uh
here, I'll just show you actually. So
flow means you don't want a lot of
friction when they're opting into
something, right? So, shameless plug if
you want to use my um if you want to use
my link, you get everything for free,
but uh for for go high level and all my
ad [__] and all my templates, but this
would be this would be an example of low
friction. So, let's say we run an ad to
a to a landing page. Somebody clicks get
instant access and they come here and
there's just two questions, name and
phone number, right? There's not very
much friction here. But, if we wanted to
add friction and get higher quality
leads, we'd we'd ask a bunch of
qualifying questions here like what's
your business name? Uh how long have you
been in business for? What's your
revenue level? how soon are you looking
to take action? So, that would create a
lot of friction and make our cost per
lead go way through the roof, but we'd
be getting higher quality leads. The
thing is, if you're just starting out
and you're spending less than a couple
hundred a day in ad spend, you don't
want to add a bunch of friction. You
want to let flow come first. So, I would
literally just put name and number and
that's it. If you're going to run them
through a landing page, just name and
number, collect the lead information,
and then call them, right? If you're
more experienced with running ads, then
you already know how friction and flow
works. But the more friction you add,
the the more your leads are going to
cost, but the higher the lead cost will
be or excuse me, the more quality the
lead will be, right? So, if you just let
the if you let the floodgates open and
let's just say you just run a simple
Facebook form ad, you're going to get a
[__] ton of leads, but they're going to
be very low quality and you're going to
have to go filter through all of them to
find the good ones as opposed to just
coming in here and adding a bunch of
friction. Your cost per lead is going to
go way up, but the leads that do come in
are going to be significantly higher
quality leads and way more ready to buy.
Okay, so a couple core lessons I've
learned uh learned along the way. Nobody
knows how met ads work. Like if anyone
pretends they do, they they really
don't. Like I'm over here just talking
about my experience and you know $200 or
$300,000 of ad spend. But these gurus
out here like they can give you the
basics and like core lessons, but again
there are so many conflicting opinions
and Facebook really is a black box which
is why like I always just say test it
and focus on creative over everything
else. Facebook's AI is so good now that
creative matters more than anything else
and the creative will literally do the
targeting for you. Okay? And also, like
I just said, flow before friction. The
most common thing I see inside my
community and coaching and all that is
people messing with [__] that's working.
If you have an ad that is working, like
I probably I've probably lost my ad
account four or five times now. It it's
ridiculous. Like not lost my ad account,
but just messed up a winning campaign
because I was trying to optimize it and
make it better. If you have something
that is working, do not touch it.
Please, for the love of God, do not
touch it. Just let it run and let it
rip. Okay? Like, it's so easy to mess up
a campaign. It's unbelievable. Okay? And
lastly, be a Chad, not a virgin. This is
the best picture. If there was one
picture of how to be a media buyer, it
would be this one, right? Uh before me
and my partner actually became partners,
this was literally him. Like, he was
trying to optimize for CPM cost and do
like 1% lookalike audiences and all this
nerdy Facebook [__] And I just
literally had a good creative and I just
let broad targeting rip and I did
significantly better, right? Obviously,
there's there's nuances to this and
we're testing different audiences and
we're always testing stuff, but if
you're just starting out and you're not
an experienced media buyer, just go
broad. Like, literally, just go broad.
You don't like Facebook's AI is so good.
Just let Facebook do the work. Trust
Zuck before you trust yourself. Okay.
Um, so that's it. Super super super
simple. And go rip.